fsoft.com.vn 2011-11-01

# Privacy Statement

**This statement applies to FPT Software World Wide.**

FPT Software understands that you, our customers and/or visitors of our website, are particularly aware of securities in relation to your personal information. Within our effort we respect and commit to protect your personal information and therefore we have created this privacy statement in order to commit our company's opinion on privacy. 

You can assess or visit our website at any time without informing us who you are or providing us any personal information. We do not attempt to track your personal information in order to identify you, but gathering these contact information in order to make up the web traffic routing, to diagnose problems with server for administration of our website, to better understand how you interact with our website and services and to re-design and upgrade the website for better use. These are not personal information but the number of assessments to website and the length of each assessment. 

We do not collect any of your personal information such as name, age, address, means of transportation, telephone number or email address when you are visiting our website, except when you agree to provide them or you may turn off cookies in your browser. Like many websites, when you access to our websites, we will use “website assessment diary”- a cookie technology to collect additional website usage data. A cookie is a small data file that we transfer to your computer to facilitate your assessment to our websites. Most Internet browsers automatically accept cookies. You can instruct your browser, by editing its options, to stop accepting cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie from the websites you visit. 

Started in 1988 as a division of FPT Corporation, the biggest ICT Company in Vietnam, FPT Software has developed rapidly and become a company of international stature. We have presence in 3 biggest cities of Vietnam (Ha Noi, Da Nang, Ho Chi Minh City) and in all major IT markets including Japan (Tokyo, Osaka), South East Asia (Singapore, Malaysia, Thailand, the Philippines), Europe (France), United States and Australia. 

Our purposes to collect your personal information are: 

  * To further fulfill your requirements on products and services  

  * To contact you with the aim of developing a business relationship  

  * To feedback to your idea and/or to provide you relevant information at your requirements  

  * To contact you for marketing purpose such as customer surveys.  

  * To inform you about our company  

  * To obey regulations in applicable laws   

**Security Commitment  
**  
FPT Software commits to secure your personal information with all securities measures in place. The measures will help protecting data from the misuse, loss, leakage and/or alteration of information. Your personal information is access restricted to authorized FPT Software's personnel for the sake of providing service at your requirements and/or for FPT Software's audit, internal audit and for the purpose of law obligation. We strictly require our personnel, in any way, to protect your personal information and have use all measurements, technology and recognized security process for this purpose in compliance with government authorizations' regulations.   
Third party 

**Links to other websites  
**  
This site contains links to other websites but they are neither FPT Software's websites nor under control of FPT Software. FPT Software is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content and transactions of such websites. You are required to read carefully the Privacy part of those linked websites to assure that you have fully understood the way of personal information collection and sharing before providing your own information. You shall take all responsibility of risk that may incur when using those websites. 

**Changes on Privacy Statements  
**  
FPT Software reserves the rights to change, modify, add or remove in whole or in part this Privacy Statement at its sole discretion, at any time. Therefore, you are responsible for regularly reviewing this statement. Changes of this Privacy Statements will be posted into this websites so as to notice you about them. These changes will also be effective when they are posted. Your continued use of this statement constitutes your agreement to all such terms. 

**Contacting the website**

If you have any questions about our Privacy Statement or about how to protect your personal information, you can contact to FPT Software Co.Ltd.
